<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MaterialYou Catalog</string>
    <string name="app_title">Material3 Catalog</string>
    <string name="overview_progress_indicators">Progress indicators inform users about the status of ongoing processes, such as loading an app or submitting a form.</string>
    <string name="overview_text_font">Use typography to make writing legible and beautiful. Material\'s default type scale includes contrasting and flexible styles to support a wide range of use cases.</string>
    <string name="overview_chips">Chips can show multiple interactive elements together in the same area, such as a list of selectable movie times, or a series of email contacts. There are four types of chips: assist, filter, input, and suggestion.</string>
    <string name="not_available_message">Jetpack Compose is not yet available.</string>
    <string name="overview_buttons">Buttons help people initiate actions, from sending an email, to sharing a document, to liking a post.</string>
    <string name="overview_card">Cards contain content and actions that relate information about a subject.</string>
    <string name="overview_textfield">Text fields allow users to enter text into a UI. They typically appear in forms and dialogs.</string>
    <string name="overview_sliders">Sliders allow users to make selections from a range of values.</string>
    <string name="overview_navigationrail">Navigation rails provide access to primary destinations in apps when using tablet and desktop screens.</string>
    <string name="overview_appbar">Top app bars display information and actions at the top of a screen.\nA bottom app bar displays navigation and key actions at the bottom of mobile screens.</string>
    <string name="overview_dialog">Dialogs provide important prompts in a user flow.</string>
    <string name="overview_animated_visibility">AnimatedVisibility is used when animating content change in layout and animating appearance / disappearance.</string>
    <string name="overview_animate_as_state">AnimateAsState is used when it is state-based and happens during composition, animating single values and animation is finite.</string>
    <string name="overview_animated_content">AnimatedContent is used when animating content change in layout and swapping content based on state.</string>
    <string name="overview_update_transition">UpdateTransition is used when it is state-based and happens during composition. It is animating multiple values simultaneously and animation is finite.</string>
    <string name="overview_tooltip">Tooltips are informative, specific, and action-oriented text labels that provide contextual support</string>
    <string name="rich_tooltips_message">Rich tooltips bring attention to a particular element of feature that warrants the user\'s focus. It supports multiple lines of informational text.</string>
</resources>